Guide to the Calhoun College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2016 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student records for the Classes of 2003 to 2016, Accession 2018-A-0078
  - Class of 2006
    - Stumpf, Simon Maxwell, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Suplee, Ryan Mark, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Swartz, Molly Elizabeth, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Swett, Diana, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Thompson, Jeffrey Lockwood, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Thompson, Raquel Virginia, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Torres, Jesus, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Vainberg, Vladislav S., 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Velez, Yuri Esteban, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Von Hoffman, Esme Lang, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Wang, Tiffany Shiau-ting, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Ward, Andrew Alexander, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Weng, Jie, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Wilcox, Faber Watson, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Wing, Matthew James, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Wiseman, Shari Lenore, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Wu, Florence Jennifer, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Yan, Ting ting, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Yang, Christie Leigh, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Yeo, Wenshan, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Yoo, Jihn Hyun, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Yudofsky, Lynn Marie, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Zappala, Joseph Christopher, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Zhao, Lingli, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Class of 2007
    - Addo, Gilbert Cameron, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Bai, Nina Yu, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Bedolla, Deborah, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Beinecke, Benjamin Barrett, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Berlin, Laura Nicole, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Berman, Danielle, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Bhattacharyya, Shamik, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Bishop, Ian Joseph, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Bradshaw, Rachel Kirschenmann, 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Brown, Eric C., 2003-2007 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Burns, Robert Brian, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Campbell, Ashley Anderson, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Matthew Samuel, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Carlin, Elizabeth Emily, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Chai, Won B., 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Clifton, John William Andrew, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Collins, Dane Andrew, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Collura, Nicholas John, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Dautch, Leif Marcus, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Erica Rosheda, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Dean, Nathaniel Roland, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Deiters, Amanda Beth, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Djamanakova, Aigerim, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Edelman, R. David, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Elbogen, Amanda Beth, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ferrara, Albert Edward, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Finnel, Stephanie Josefina, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - First, Jacob K., 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Fisher, Mark Aaron, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Forsblom, William Brock, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Fuchs, Daniel Hochman, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Garber, Alexey, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Gary, Christopher Wayne, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Gaughen, Kara Corrigan, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Gaynon, Laura Mee Kyung, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Gelfond, Pamela Nicole, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Goldberg, Benjamin, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Greenburg, Zack O'Malley, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Haab, Nicole Justine, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Halbsgut, Lisa R., 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Heard, Ethan Johnson, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Hergenham, Michael John, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Hills, Gage Krieger, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Huang, Rawen Zhi Hong, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hyseni, Qazim, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Inglis, Robert Durden, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Isaacson, Susanna, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - James, Warren Patrick, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Jeffries, Melissa Anne, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Juel, Megan Frances, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kahn, Suzanne Maria, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Kalisha, Grace Tsitsi, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Khan, Abdullah, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Khong, Rachel Nai Xin, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Knox, David Lebron, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Kochanek, Ashley Rene, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Kucera, James Michael, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lachman, Matthew Edward, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Lapeira, Javier, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Lapinig, Christopher Myron, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Larson, Mark Richard, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - LeClerc, William Thomas, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Leonard, Marcus Anthony, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Lespinasse, Danielle Marie, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Levendis, Marissa Lydia, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Dain Evan, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Li, Puyao, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Lieb, Brynne Hawley, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Littlefield, Casey Anne, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Loew, Lorena-withdrawn, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Machida, Nicholas Kenji, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Minichino, Nicholas Anthony, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Thomas Marriott, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Murphy, Glenn Edgar, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Nkansah, Michael Kwasi, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Ongun, Sarah Iliana, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Park, Dongyung, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Pinto, Gabriella Elaine, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Polland, Allison Rachel, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Ponganutree, Daniya, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Price, Sarah Marie, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Prouty, Brooks, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Quinlan, Adriane Schaap, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Quinn, John Charles, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Sadighian, David Bijan, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Schachar, Eli Banks, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Shankar, Maya Uma, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Shvartsman, Michael, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Slaughter, Christine Lynn, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sparks, Whitney Watkins, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Srinivasan, Amia Parvathi, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Steinberg, Elizabeth Anne, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Stemler, Philip Patrick, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Stewart, James Ryan, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Swartout, Robin Lynn, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Sykes, Aida Mwajua, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Thomas, Daniel Edward, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Tian, David Cong, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Trent, Kimberly Renee, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Tross, Robert, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Tsang, Christine Shih-Chi, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Valache, Carmen Paula, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - van der Linden, Jared Henricus, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Vinado, Christina, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Walker, Allison Edna, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Wan, Tiffany Ashley, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Wasmoen, Nikolaus Lee, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Weigandt, Thomas Patrick, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Weisfeld, Daniel R., 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Winkler, Christopher S., 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Winkler-Rhoades, Ruben, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Wojnarwsky, Amy Marie, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Wu, Qiong, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Wyman, Katherine Maeve, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Zimmer, Carmen Maria, 2003-2007 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Class of 2008
    - Alexandrov, Nicholas, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Amodeo, Samantha, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Leah Mahealani, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Angulo, Luis, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Ash, Andrew, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Babic, Milos, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Babst, James, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Bandler, Scott, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Barenbaum, Sarah, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Battey, Allison, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Best, Jennica Michelle, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bolton, Jennifer Sarah, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Boucher, Jean Francois, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Bragg, Susannah, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Burkhard, Philip, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Camarda, Michael, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Carney, Julie, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Chadwick, Edwin, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Connery, Kathryn, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Coplin, Abigail Elizabeth, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Cotter, Mark, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Cox, Brian, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Danna, Megan, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Dardig, James, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - DelVecchio, Nicholas, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Diez, Andriana, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Dowd, Caroline, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Dowling, Kathryn, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Edwards, Brian, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Engasser, William Mark, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Evans, Jared Michael, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Fiedorek, Elizabeth, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Gelblum, Madeline, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Germain, David John, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Geronemus, Rachel, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Goldmann, Noah Andrew, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Gummess, Matthew, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Hahn, Esther, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Hamilton, Jared, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Hammond, Marcus, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Harris, Ruben, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Hays, Erin, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Heller, Ann, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Hickox, Frances, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Hill, Elisabeth, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Howard, Margaret, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Jackson, Jason, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Jamison, Rachel, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Jiang, Xiaodong, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Jicha, Henry, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Johnson, Erin, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Kerth, Robert, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Kim, Sung, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Levi, Daniel, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Lewis, Amanda, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Liford, Robert Lawrence, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Lomnitz, Elisa, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Lopez Fadul, Valeria Alexandra E., 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Madden, Reid, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Mason, Daniel, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Morrison, Daniel T., 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - McChristian, Andrea, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - McIntosh, David Alexander, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Meller, Hilla, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Mirza, Isa, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Mittermiller, Paul, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Newman-Wise, Alexander, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Nguyen, Khang, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Nunez, Salvador, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Page, Robert Louis, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Phillips, Emily, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Pierce, Mallory, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Pitts, Freya, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Podell, Jamie, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Poland, Eugenia B., 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Ponce, Ashley, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Poter, Jessica, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Rabinovitch, Jason, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Rahman, Taieef, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Ramamoorthy, Joe, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Retzloff, Bradley S., 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Richter, Michael T., 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Rosenthal, Claudia, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Schawlowski, Diana, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Schmidt, Michael, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Schulmeister, James, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Schwarz, Kristen, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Schwink, Steven C., 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Seyhan, Hasan, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Shackleton, David, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Shapiro, David, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Shapiro, Hillary, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Smith, David, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Smith, Erica, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Smith, GeoAnna, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Stovall, Alyssa Lynn, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Strother, Matthew, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Su, Xiaowei, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Sun, Jing, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Tezgul, Mehmet Adil, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Thomey, Matthew, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Tran, Thuy Trang, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Tsang, Keith, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Turner-Evans, Daniel, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Ulanova, Jane, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Vogelsang, John, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Washabaugh, Kyle, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Watson, Candice, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Wehner, Mackenzie, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Weng, Jeffrey, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Wu, Tian Ying, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Zeng, Yuting, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Class of 2009
    - Acker, Margo, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Agbi, Clarence, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Allan, Lora Nicole, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Robert, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Anastos-Wallen, Rebecca, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Arma, Ehsan, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Baer, Matthew, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Becton, Grace, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bierce, Jennifer Butler, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bloom, Sonali, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Bloom-Feshbach, Kimberly, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Brandes, Stephen, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Braverman, Genna Michelle, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Brendlinger, Kurt, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Bruene, Jacob, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Butler, Alisha, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Campbell, Colin, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Canals, Ofelia M., 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Cantrell, Michael, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Castiglione, Erik, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Charokopos, Antonios, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Clark, Nathaniel, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Clarke, Pheobe S., 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Emily, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Crawford, Elizabeth, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Cuellar, Joseph, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - DiMaio, Jonathan, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Dull, Ian, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Earle, Katherine, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Earp, Brian, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Ensslen, Daniel Robert Carman, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Farley, Kristin, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Ferguson, Susanna, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Fishel, William, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Fong, Brandon, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Ford, Daniel Bailey, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Friend, Stephanie, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Fromson, Daniel, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Goldman, Simon, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Hann, Bradley, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Hartzell, Jennifer, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Hickenbottom, Kevin, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Hidalgo, Sylvana, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Ho, Joanne, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Hu, Jane, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Hume, Lilah, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Igweatu, Ugonna, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Im, Erica, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Jenn, Alexandre, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Ji,Zhaodan, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Jiminez, Danielle, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Jiminez, Jonathan, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Jones, Kerry, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Kant, David, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Kim, Byol, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Kim, Molly, 2005-2009 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - King, Alexander, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Klinkhachorn, Tanya, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Langat, Maria, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Lawlor, Kathleen, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - LeCesne, Adrian, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Lee, Matthew, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Lefkovits, Alexandria, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Li, Dan, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Li, Rosa, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Luberoff, Eli, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Luis, Marcos Antonio, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Lund, Dane, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Ly, Catherine, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Martinez, Karla, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - McCall, Kristen Ellen, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Meckel, Katherine Hunter, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mellon, Diana, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Miller, Jacob William, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Miller, Kasdin Elizabeth, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Mills, Bradley James, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Muirhead, Justin, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Nagem, Raymond, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Newman, David, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Nwoke, Ifeoma, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Oakman, Nicole, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - O'Brien, Sarah, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Parks, Anna, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Pedroza, Juan Jose, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Piawah, Sorbarikor, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Pierce, Laura, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Pilkerton, James, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Price, Robert, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Pyle, Bryce, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Ray, Ellen, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Reisman, Marisa, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Rogach, Nataliya, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Russell, Ryan, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Samuel, Andrew, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Santoro, Thomas, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Savello, Caroline, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Schwab, Mark, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Seymour, Lee, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Shearer, Hannah, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Sherill, Paul, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Shieh, Richard, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Shue, Ann, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Stegmaier, Andrew, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Stupay, Kristen Larissa, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Szabo, Alison, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Taylor, Jennifer, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Tittman, Sarah, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Totapally, Swetha, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Totti, Jaime, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Ugoji, Keside, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Walker, Alex, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Wang, Yizi, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Weissler, Emily, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Wihldahl, Christopher, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Wilk, Kristen, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Wirth, Stephen, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Wood, Monica Jing, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Xu, Anne, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Yale, Christopher, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Yang, Zhiyuan, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Young, Christian, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Yu, Victoria, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Zarecki, Domenic, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Class of 2010
    - Abell, Thomas, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Adams, Katherine, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Allee, Spencer, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Anoliefo, Kenechukwu, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Berlin, Ari, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Bregman, Jonathan, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Briscoe, Kyle, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Canulli, Alexandra, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Caplan, Rachel, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Chau, Elie, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Chen, Jason, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Clements, Caitlin, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Cohen, Drew, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Cohen, Hilary, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Daly, Sinead, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Davidson, Victoria, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Davis, Caroline, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - DeLee, Daniel, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Duboff, Samuel, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Duffy, Caitlyn, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Erickson, Jaqueline Rose, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Faisal, Farzana, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Fischbeck, Robert, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Fukuyama, Julia, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Gelerntner, Daniel, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Gerrand, Tess, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Gibson, Theodore, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Gillespie, Kenya, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Glassman, Amanda Katie, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Gottesdiener, Laura, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Griffen, Scott, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Grigoroglou, Soultana, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Gruber, Robert, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Gupta, Sameer, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Haselkorn, Joshua, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Hefferon, Lauren, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Henly, Alice, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Henriques, Bryan, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Ho, Wen Yu, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Holbrook, Andrew, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Hunter, Lauren, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Isenberg, Rex, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Jackson, Lindsey, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Jasso, Troy, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Jee, Justin, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Kairon, Dilsher P., 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Karinen, Jennifer, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Kelly, Joseph, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Korb, Gregory, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Larsen, Amy, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Lee, John, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Liang, Han, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Libertin, Michael, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Lihan, Sarah, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Loi, Charles, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Manners-Weber, David, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Marquis, Joseph Pierre, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - McTernan, Andrew, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Mirabal, Michelle, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 68)